Thank you. Well now it's time for our last inductee and as they all say it's
last but certainly not least.
Many people asked us if they could be the one to induct Dr. Mohan Bafna.
But we thought that with his stature as patriarch of this great family, it
would be fitting for his son, Shiresh, to induct his father.
Shiresh received his BS/MEA Operations Management from Weatherbit School of
Management at Case Western Reserve University.
He is the owner of Janko Tech, Raptite and Solon which provides complete
imaging services for professional photographers
and is an importer distributor of packaging films, envelopes and supplies for
the shipping industry.
Where are you Shiresh?
Come on.
I know there's a person who's not represented and probably wouldn't mind
talking to you.
Alright Shiresh if you could introduce any of your father into the hall.